You must have heard about helmet Shiv Vilas,
but there are so many people around us and
in our family who
consider helmet as just a burden on the head and
ignore wearing it while riding. To
make such people aware, ICICI
Lombard has started an initiative,
Top the Helmet Students. To participate in this,
go to righttosafety.com and
register your loved ones who make excuses for not wearing helmet.
ICICI Lombard will
send a personal ISN note to such people and will tell them the
importance of helmet. So why are you losing it,
register
on righttosafety.com and participate
for helmet awareness and always wear a good
quality helmet while riding a bike.